Guide to the Facilities Management Department records, 1924-ongoing UA.10.05.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Architectual Drawings, 2
  - Language (also called Old Law, originally Law School Building), 13
    - Preliminary Plans of Law Building: First Floor, Second Floor Plans; Third Floor, Basement Plans, undated; cuid122; 2 Sheets (Oversize-folder 17)
    - Law School Building: Schedule for Interior Wood Doors, 1929 December 13; cuid123; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 17)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 3041
    - Law School Building: Elevation, 1929 May 2; cuid124; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 17)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 3045
    - Law School Building, 1930 April 1; cuid125; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 17)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 3047
    - Law School Building: Judges Stand Details, [1929] August 26; cuid126; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 17)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 3048
    - Law School Building, [1929] August 14; cuid127; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 18)
    - Law School Building: Floor Plans; Elevation; Framing Plans, 1931 August 22; cuid128; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 18)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 3001-3004
    - Law School Building: Floor Plans, 1929 July 1; cuid129; 2 Sheets (Oversize-folder 18)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 3011-3012
  - Lilly Library
    - Lilly Library 1 of 2, cuid185; 16 Sheets (Oversize-folder 35)
    - Lilly Library 2 of 2, cuid186; 32 Sheets (Oversize-folder 36)
  - Old Chem, 14
    - Chemistry Building: Light and Power Wiring Riser Diagram, 1930 July 3; cuid130; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 19)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 5558
    - Chemistry Building: Direct Current Laboratory Wiring Riser Diagram, 1930 July 3; cuid131; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 19)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 5559
    - Chemistry Building: First Floor; Second Floor; Third Floor; Basement Plans, 1927 September 19; cuid132; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 19)
    - Chemistry Building, 1927 September 19; cuid133; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 19)
    - Chemistry Building, undated; cuid134; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 19)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 5562
  - Perkins Library and Rubenstein Library (originally Library Building), 15
    - Library Building: First Floor Plan, 1930 August 5; cuid135; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 20)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2002
    - Library Building: Elevation, 1929 September 24; cuid136; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 20)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2006-2008
    - Library Building: Floor Plans, 1930 April 9; cuid137; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 20)
      White paper copy; sheet numbers: 2001-2005
    - Alterations and Additions to Library Building: Floor Plans; Elevations and Exterior Details; Elevations; Section and Window Details on Elvation DD, 1949 May 16; cuid138; 8 Sheets (Oversize-folder 20)
      White paper copy; sheet numbers: 1-8
    - Library Building: Second Floor; Third Floor; Roof Plans, 1930 August 5; cuid139; 3 Sheets (Oversize-folder 20)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2003-2005
    - Library Building: Plumbing, Heating, and Electrical Work, 1929 October 9; cuid140; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 20)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2047-2050
    - Library Building: Details of Main Reading Room, 1929 February 15; cuid141; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 21)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2062
    - Library Building: Deteails Reading Room and Passage, 1928 September 8; cuid142; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 21)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2016
    - Library Buraeu: Proposed Metal Bookstacks in Library Building, undated; cuid143; 9 Sheets (Oversize-folder 21)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 1-8
    - Library Building: Plan of Stair Tower, 1928 September 10; cuid144; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 21)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2053
    - Library Building: Stairs, 1929 July 9; cuid145; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 22)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2012
  - Physics, 16
    - Alterations and Additions to Physics Building: Sub Basement and Ground Floor Plans, First and Second Floor Plans, Riser Diagram and Details, 1950 November 28; cuid146; 3 Sheets (Oversize-folder 23)
    - Alterations and Additions to Physics Building: Sub Basement and Ground Floor Plans, First and Second Floor Plans, 1950 November 28; cuid147; 2 Sheets (Oversize-folder 23)
    - Alterations and Additions to Physics Building: Sub Basement and Ground Floor Plans; First Floor Plan and Second Floor Plan; Riser Diagram, Plot Plan and Details, 1950 November 28; cuid148; 3 Sheets (Oversize-folder 23)
    - Physics Building: Assorted, 1950 November 28; cuid149; 34 Sheets (Oversize-folder 23)
    - Physics Building: Elevation; Floor Plans; Laboratory Wiring Riser Diagram; Lights and Power Wiring Riser Diagram, 1930 July 19; cuid150; 8 Sheets (Oversize-folder 23)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 7006, 7011-7014, 7039-7041
  - Sociology/Psychology (originally Botany and Zoology Building), 17
    - Botany and Zoology Building: Floor Plans; Elevation; School of Religion Building: Elevation, 1930 December 22; cuid151; 14 Sheets (Oversize-folder 24)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 4501-4506, 1506, 4507-4508.
      Includes one sheet of School of Religion building plans.
    - Botany and Zoology Building: Framing Plans, 1929 August 23; cuid152; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 24)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 4509-4513
    - Botany and Zoology Building: Elevations; Electrical Plans, 1931 March 13; cuid153; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 24)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 4522, E817-21
    - Botany and Zoology Building: Floor Plans, 1930 May 28; cuid154; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 24)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 4518-4521
    - Botany and Zoology Building: Front Elevation of Main Gable and Gables "A" and "B"; Rear Elevation Gable "C" small gables, 1929 April 29; cuid155; 2 Sheets (Oversize-folder 25)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 4514, 4516
  - Wallace Wade Stadium (originally Stadium), 18
    - FS Detail of Connections, 1929 August 26; cuid168; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 29)
    - Wall at Back of Press; Scout and Guest Boxes, 1929 August 12; cuid169; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 29)
  - West Campus Union (originally Union Building), 19
    - Alterations to Union Building, 1953 December 4; cuid156; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 26)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 1
    - Union Building: D.H. Blackboard and Picture Screen Detail, 1927 August 27; cuid157; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 26)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 328
    - Union Building: Floor Plans, 1929 March 23; cuid158; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 26)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 500, 502-4
    - Union Building: Elevation Facing Library Building; Elevation, 1929 January 31; cuid159; 2 Sheets (Oversize-folder 26)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 505-506
    - Union Building: Sections and Elevations; Framing Plans, 1929 January 31; cuid160; 7 Sheets (Oversize-folder 26)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 507-513
    - Union Building: Corner Stone, 1928 May 7; cuid161; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 26)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 604
    - Union Building: Interior Details, 1929 July 12; cuid162; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 26)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 639
    - Union Building: Interior Details, 1929 July 15; cuid163; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 26)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 641
    - Union Building: College Store Counters, 1930 February 24; cuid164; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 26)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 662
    - Union Building: Layout of Kitchen, 1928 June 1; cuid165; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 27)